Inventory of the Maupin-Washington Papers 1732-1932
Earl Gregg Swem Library, College of William and Mary
- Personal and Business Correspondence of Peter Grayson Washington, 1835-1866, n.d. (Box 1-2)
  - Personal and Business Correspondence, 1854. (Box-folder 1:5)
    - T[homas] J[ames] D[uncan] Fuller, Calais, [Maine], to Peter Grayson Washington, Washington, [D.C.], 21 September 1854., 3 pages. ALS. (Box-folder 1:5)
      Believes he won his close election; asks about a Customs House at Ellsworth, and the appointment of Joseph H. Jordun.
    - John Cadwalader, Philad[elphi]a, [Pennsylvania], to Peter Grayson Washington, n.p. Discusses his margin of victory in the election, 11 October 1854., 3 pages. ALS. (Box-folder 1:5)
    - J[ohn] O'Fallon, St. Louis, [Missouri], to Peter Grayson Washington, Ass[istant] Secretary of the Treasury, [Washington, D.C.], 16 October 1854., 1 page. ALS. (Box-folder 1:5)
      Introduces George Th. McGunesh[?].
    - John Robbins, Jr., Kensington, Phila[delphia], [Pennsylvania], to Peter Grayson Washington, Assistant Sec[retary] of [the] Treasury, [Washington, D.C.], 21 October 1854., 1 page. ALS. (Box-folder 1:5)
      Asks him again for a statement of matters relating to the tariff.
    - Geo[rge] Read Riddle, Wilmington, Delaware, to Peter Grayson Washington, n.p., 6 November 1854., 1 page. ALS. (Box-folder 1:5)
      Needs Col. Wm. H. Jones of the Auditor's Office with him for a few days.
    - H[enry] May, Balt[im]o[re], [Maryland], to "Dear Colonel" [Peter Grayson Washington], n.p., 13 November [1854]., 4 pages. LS. (Box-folder 1:5)
      Thanks him for support in his campaign, which he lost because of illness.
    - J[ohn] C[adwalader], Phil[adelphi]a [Pennsylvania], to Peter Grayson W[ashington], n.p., 28 November 1854., 4 pages. ALS. (Box-folder 1:5)
      Discusses various appointments, and a problem about a stonecutter.
  - Personal and Business Correspondence, 1855. (Box-folder 2:1)
    - Daniel Lord, New York, [New York], to Col. [Peter Grayson] Washington, n.p., 27 January 1855., 1 page. ALS. (Box-folder 2:1)
      Introduces Mr. Cunard.
    - W. Meade Addison, Balt[im]o[re, Maryland], to Peter Grayson Washington, Ass[istan]t Sec[retar]y of [the] Treas[ur]y, [Washington, D.C.], 8 February 1855., 2 pages. ALS. (Box-folder 2:1)
      Could not keep their appointment; asks for the results of Washington's interview with the Secretary so he can tell the Chief Justice.
    - Jno. Swift, Philad[elphi]a, [Pennsylvania], to Peter Grayson Washington, n.p. 8 February [18]55., 1 page. ALS. (Box-folder 2:1)
      Sent the bond required to Vincent's case and asks for Washington's help.
    - Lucius] B[enedict] Peck, Woodstock, [Vermont?], to Peter Grayson Washington, Washington, [D.C.], 19 February 1855., 3 pages. ALS. (Box-folder 2:1)
      Thanks Washington for his letter of sympathy on Peck's wife's death; suggests he write Anna, who is in New York.
    - Reverdy Johnson, Balt[imore, Maryland], to Peter Grayson Washington, Ass[istan]t Sec[retar]y [of the Treasury, Washington, D.C.], 19 February [18]55., 3 pages. ALS. (Box-folder 2:1)
      Offers to sell his residence for the Court House that Congress has just authorized.
    - John B. Weller, Senate Chamber, [Washington, D.C.], to Peter Grayson Washington, n.p., 26 February 1855., 1 page. ALS. (Box-folder 2:1)
      Recommends Addison for a clerk's position in Washington's office.
    - W. F. Allen, Oswego[?], New York, to Peter Grayson Washington, Ass[istan]t Sec[retar]y of [the] Treas[ur]y, [Washington, D.C.], 15 March 1855., 1 page. ALS. (Box-folder 2:1)
      Introduces Lt. John G. Bond, who is on his way to join his ship in Norfolk, [Virginia].
    - Hendrick B[radley] Wright, Wilkes Barre, Pennsylvania, to Peter Grayson Washington, Ass[istan]t Treasury Dept., [Washington, D.C.], 20 March 1855., 1 page. ALS. (Box-folder 2:1)
      Forwarded the notice of appointment to Mr. Miles, but has not heard from him.
    - John Robbins, Jr., Kensington, Phila[delphia, Pennsylvania], Peter Grayson Washington, Assistant Secretary of [the] Treasury, [Washington, D.C.], 23 March 1855., 1 page. ALS. (Box-folder 2:1)
      Introduces Casper Schedler, who has business with Mr. Guthrie on importing goods.
    - John W. Duvall, Portland, [?], to Peter Grayson Washington, [Washington, D.C.], 28 March 1855., 2 pages. ALS. (Box-folder 2:1)
      Introduces Mr. Stone[?], a temporary Inspector at the Port of Portland, who wants an increase in pay from $2.00 per day.
    - S. Hamilton, Savannah, [Georgia], to Peter C. [sic] Washington, Ass[istan]t Sec[retar]y of the Treasury, Washington, [D.C.], 6 April 1855., 3 pages. ALS. (Box-folder 2:1)
      Discusses action in the House of Representatives regarding payment of the Texas Debt, and asks for information for an article he is writing on the subject.
    - M[oses] H. Grinnell, New York, [New York], to Peter A. [sic] Washington, Assistant Secretary of the Treasury, Washington, [D.C.], 14 May 1855., 2 pages. ALS. (Box-folder 2:1)
      Introduces Anthony Thornton, who is in Washington to arrange about bonded stores in New York.
    - Colin M[acrae] Ingersoll, New Haven, Connecticut, to Peter Grayson Washington, n.p., 22 May 1855., 1 page. ALS. (Box-folder 2:1)
      Discusses appointment of the Superintendent of the Customs House.
    - H[enry] May, Balt[im]o[re, Maryland], to Colonel [Peter Grayson Washington], n.p., 7 June [1855?], 1 page. ALS. (Box-folder 2:1)
      Thanks him for the item for Mr. Matson[?]; comments on the appointment of Buckingham Smith to Spain.
    - W[illiam] H[enry] Witte, Phila[delphia, Pennsylvania], to Peter Grayson Washington, As[sistan]t Sec[retary] of the Treasury, [Washington, D.C.], 9 June 1855., 2 pages. ALS. (Box-folder 2:1)
      Asks Washington's cooperation in getting a leave of absence for Capt. J. C. Kretchmon[?].
    - Geo[re] W[allace] Jones, Dubuque, Iowa, to Peter Grayson Washington, As[sistan]t Sec[retar]y [of the] Treas[ur]y, Washington, D.C., 29 June 1855., 4 pages. ALS. (Box-folder 2:1)
      Encloses a letter as an example of how Washington and Mr. Guthrie need to have clerks be more respectful; discusses question of lamps around Mr. Quigley's office.
    - John Mckeon, New York, [New York], to Peter Grayson Washington, n.p., 5 July 1855., 1 page. ALS. (Box-folder 2:1)
      Supports Capt. Hunter's[?] request for a transfer from New York to Lake Ontario.
    - W. B. Caldwell, Louisville, Kentucky, to Peter Grayson Washington, Washington City, D.C., 8 July 1855., 2 pages. ALS. (Box-folder 2:1)
      Thanks Washington for the 3 volumes on Indians; discusses local politics.
    - Geo[rge] P. Kane, Baltimore, [Maryland], to Peter Grayson Washington, Washington, D.C., 11 July 1855., 1 page. ALS. (Box-folder 2:1)
      Asks for assistance in a matter he has written about before.
    - Horation King, 1st P[ost] M[aster] G[eneral], Appointment Office, P.O. Department, [Washington, D.C.], to Peter Grayson Washington, Acting Secretary [of the] Treasury, Washington, [D.C.], 14 August [18]55., 1 page. LS. (Box-folder 2:1)
      Mr. Brown has been removed as Postmaster at Brandenburg, Meade County, Kentucky, and William I. Mays appointed.
    - John B. Floyd, New York, [New York], to Peter Grayson Washington, n.p., 9 September 1855., 2 pages. LS. (Box-folder 2:1)
      Requests that the salary of a bookkeeper be increased.
    - T[homas] J[ames] D[uncan] Fuller, Calais, Maine, to Peter Grayson Washington, D.C., 11 September 1855., 1 page. ALS. (Box-folder 2:1)
      Describes his recent campaign in Maine.
    - E. G. Eastman, Nashville, [Tennessee], to Peter Grayson Washington, Washington, D.C., 12 September 1855., 1 page. ALS. (Box-folder 2:1)
      Needs the true story of the money advanced for Sam Medary's "outfit"; discusses the recent campaign.
    - W[illia]m H[enry] Aspinwall, New York, [New York], to Peter Grayson Washington, n.p., 7 November 1855., 2 pages. ALS. (Box-folder 2:1)
      Would like an appointment soon to discuss greater facilities for freight shipped to California.
    - J[ohn] Ross Browne, San Francisco, California, to Peter Grayson Washington, Assistant Secretary of the Treasury, [Washington, D.C.], 20 November 1855., 3 pages. ALS. (Box-folder 2:1)
      Glowing report on the New Customs House; discusses the failure of Landers & Brenham; asks for authority to purge prominent people "of their iniquities"; would like a position elsewhere.
    - James Ross Snowden, Mint of the United States, Philadelphia, [Pennsylvania], to Peter Grayson Washington, Washington City [D.C.], 18 December 1855., 3 pages. ALS. (Box-folder 2:1)
      Needs a complete set of the Laws of Congress for his work on public medals presented; lists some presentations he need material on.
    - Asa Biggs, Senate Chamber, [Washington, D.C.], to Peter Grayson Washington, Ass[istan]t Sec[retar]y of the Treasury, [Washington, D.C.], 18 December 1855., 1 page. ALS. (Box-folder 2:1)
      Asks for publication information on "Register of California Claims, 1846-47" and where it can be obtained.
  - Personal and Business Correspondence, 1856. (Box-folder 2:2)
    - Samuel L. M. Barlow, New York, [New York], to Peter Grayson Washington, n.p., 2 January 1856., 2 pages. ALS. (Box-folder 2:2)
      Mess[rs.] Aspinwall are very angry with the President [Pierce], and feel the only course left to get the withdrawal of Mexico's protest is by paying a large sum; both the writer and "friend Tyler" will lose their contingent fees.
    - P[hilip] Phillips, Washington, [D.C.], to Peter Grayson Washington, [Washington, D.C.], 9 January 1856., 1 page. ALS. (Box-folder 2:2)
      Introduces Mr. Gould, who has letters from Mobile, [Alabama], regarding the Marine Hospital.
    - Mortimer[?] Livingston, New York, [New York], to Peter Grayson Washington, Washington, [D.C.], 11 January 1856., 1 page. ALS. (Box-folder 2:2)
      Asks for help in getting duties waived on [some gold or silver] plate sent from England to Captain William Wallace of Baltimore.
    - H[enry] S[helton] Sanford, New York, [New York], to Peter Grayson Washington, n.p., 11 March [18]56., 1 page. ALS. (Box-folder 2:2)
      Thanks Washington for the financial reports, and the statements concerning the guano trade.
    - W[illia]m Coventry H. Waddell, St. Denis Hotel, New York, [New York], to Peter Grayson Washington, n.p., 12 March [18]56., 1 page. ALS. (Box-folder 2:2)
      Encloses important message for Mr. Cochrane, Surveyor of the Customs at New York.
    - Jo[h]n Thomson Mason, Annapolis, [Maryland], to "dear sir," 18 March 1856., 2 pages. ALS. (Box-folder 2:2)
      Withdraws his recommendation that the office of Inspector of Customs in Annapolis be restored.
    - John J. Cisco, Office of the Assistant Treasurer, U.S., New York, New York, to Peter Grayson Washington, Ass[istan]t Secretary of the Treasury, Washington, D.C., 20 March 1856., 1 page. ALS. (Box-folder 2:2)
      Introduces Jeremiah Milbank, merchant, who is in Washington regarding the debt of Texas.
    - John McKeon, New York, [New York], to Peter Grayson Washington, n.p., 3 June 1856., 1 page. ALS. (Box-folder 2:2)
      Has not received an answer to his request that Hunter not be sent to New Orleans.
    - Tho[ma]s H. Holt, Willards Hotel, [Washington, D.C.], to 'My Dear Sir,' 9 June 1856., 1 page. ALS. (Box-folder 2:2)
      Encloses an invitation to his wedding.
    - Joseph Lane, Washington City [D.C.], to W. L. Gaylord, n.p., 10 June 1856., 1 page. ALS. (Box-folder 2:2)
      Has just returned from Cincinnati, [Ohio], convention; will send Riggs & Co. a check tomorrow; the McRea papers were returned to Anderson.
    - Jno. R. Chambliss, Greensville, [?], to [?], 16 June 1856., 1 page. ANS. (Box-folder 2:2)
      Concerns the letter of Mr. W. McCabb.
    - John M. Mott, U.S. Marshal, Canadaigua, [New York] to Peter Grayson Washington, n.p., 30 June 1856., 2 pages. LS. (Box-folder 2:2)
      Supports bid of Messrs. O. B. and O. S. Latham for the Customs House at Cleveland, Ohio, over that of Mr. Warren, who is described as an active "Know Nothing".
    - R[ichard] H[enry] Stanton, Maysville, Kentucky, to "My dear friend," n.p. 30 June 1856., 4 pages. ALS. (Box-folder 2:2)
      Reports the delivery of a box to Dr. Bodenheimer; describes his campaign; needs money from "our claim"; his service in the Colmesvil[?] claim is being used against him.
    - Edwin B. Morgan, House [of] Representatives, Washington, [D.C.], to Peter Grayson Washington, Washington, [D.C.], 3 July [18]56., 1 page. ALS. (Box-folder 2:2)
      Has received a telegram from Detroit that 3 American Express Co. robbers were convicted.
    - J[ohn] Bragg, Mobile, [Alabama], to Peter Grayson Washington, n.p. 10 July 1856., 1 page. ALS. (Box-folder 2:2)
      Introduces Mr. W[illia]m Alderson, who is visiting Washington in connection with the contract to build the new Customs House in Mobile.
    - Smith Pyne, J Street [Washington, D.C.?], to Mr. [Peter Grayson] Washington, n.p. 1 August 1856., 2 pages. ALS. (Box-folder 2:2)
      Asks employment for the bearer.
    - Ro[bert] Tyler, Phila[delphia, Pennsylvania], to Peter Grayson Washington, n.p., 1[?] August [18]56., 1 page. ALS. (Box-folder 2:2)
      Introduces Mr. Colbert[?].
    - A[lbert] Rust, House [of] Repr[esentative]s, [Washington, D.C.], to Peter Grayson Washington, Ass[istan]t Sec[retary] of [the] Treasury, [Washington, D.C.], 12 August 1856., 1 page. ALS. (Box-folder 2:2)
      Is sure the office at [?], Arkansas can provide copies of his accounts while Receiver of Public Moneys there.
    - John Tyler, Jr., Philadelphia, [Pennsylvania], to Peter Grayson Washington, n.p., 26 September 1856., 1 page. ALS. (Box-folder 2:2)
      Asks Washington to read two enclosures from the daily and the weekly Pennsylvanian, which have "excited attention as far north as Boston," and then give them to Mr. Guthrie.
    - W[illiam] C. Patterson, Phila[delphia, Pennsylvania], to Peter Grayson Washington, n.p., 8 November 1856., 1 page. ALS. (Box-folder 2:2)
      Asks for a copy of Gov. Nearey's[?] recent book on consular regulations.
    - John Romeyn Brodhead, New York, [New York], to Peter Grayson Washington, n.p., 21 November 1856., 1 page. ALS. (Box-folder 2:2)
      Asks for leave; hopes to see Washington in December.
    - Henry Chauncey, New York, [New York], to Peter Grayson Washington, n.p., 25 November [18]56., 1 page. ALS. (Box-folder 2:2)
      Thanks Mr. Guthrie and Washington for their aid; hopes Post Master General will have no cause to regret delaying his decision.
    - Sam[ue]l Laurence, Boston, [Massachusetts], to Peter Washington, Wash[ingto]n, D.C., 8 December 1856., 1 page. ALS. (Box-folder 2:2)
      Praises the Secretary's report, and asks for extra copies.
    - J[ohn] Van Buren, New York, [New York], to [James] Guthrie, [Washington, D.C.], 26 December 1856., 3 pages. ALS. (Box-folder 2:2)
      Writes for friends who want their lots in Ogdensburgh [sic], [New York], purchased for the new Customs House and Post Office.
  - Personal and Business Correspondence, 1857. (Box-folder 2:3)
    - John McKeon, New York, [New York], to Peter Grayson Washington, [Washington, D.C.], 3 January 1857., 1 page. ALS. (Box-folder 2:3)
      Wants 2-3 copies of the Secretary's report.
    - R. S. S. Andros, Customs House, Boston, [Massachusetts], to Peter Grayson Washington, Ass[istan]t Sec[retar]y of the Treasury, Washington, D.C.], 13 January 1857., 1 page. ALS. (Box-folder 2:3)
      Introduces Dr. Davis, Superintendent of the U.S. Marine Hospital at Boston.
    - Myra Clark Gaines, New Orleans, [Louisiana], to "My dear Sir," n.p., 15 January 1857., 1 page. ALS. (Box-folder 2:3)
      Asks his assistance in getting her son, William, a position as Inspector; asks to be remembered to Mrs. Lee.
    - J[ames] S. T. Stranahan, House [of] Rep[resen]t[ative]s, [Washington, D.C.], to Peter Grayson Washington, n.p., 2 February 1857., 1 page. ALS. (Box-folder 2:3)
      Has received Mr. Guthrie's report of the cost of the Brooklyn, [New York] P[ost] O[ffice] building, but not the letter from the Post Master Gen[era]l to Mr. Rust.
    - John C. Mather[?], New York, [New York], to Peter Grayson Washington, Assistant Sec[re]t[ar]y of the Treasury, [Washington, D.C.], 14 February 1857., 2 pages. ALS. (Box-folder 2:3)
      Introduces Mr. John Cleminshire[?] of Albany, who seeks the contract to build Customs Houses at Plattsburgh and Ogdensburgh.
    - Samuel L. M. Barlow, New York, [New York], to Peter Grayson Washington, [Washington, D.C.], 17 February 1857., 3 pages. ALS. (Box-folder 2:3)
      Introduces Mr. John W. Griffiths, who wants the appointment as architect and naval superintendent for the Treasury Department's new steamboat.
    - H. W. Rogers, Buffalo, [New York], to Col. Peter Grayson Washington, [Washington, D.C.], 28 February 1857., 2 pages. LS. (Box-folder 2:3)
      Asks for compassion for his clients, Messrs. Moores and Richards of Chicago.
    - Jno. Caperton, Washington, D.C., to Col. [Peter Grayson] Washington, [Washington, D.C.], 7 March 1857., 1 page. ALS. (Box-folder 2:3)
      Introduces G. W. Coffee, who has the support of the California delegation.
    - J[ohn] Van Buren, New York, [New York], to [Peter Grayson] Washington, [Washington, D.C.], 12 March 1857., 3 pages. ALS. (Box-folder 2:3)
      Disappointed in situation on Customs House lot in Ogdensburgh [sic], [New York].
    - T. J[ohna]th[an] Alexander, Balt[imore, Maryland], to Peter Grayson Washington, n.p., 14 March 1857., 2 pages. ALS. (Box-folder 2:3)
      Regrets Washington's retirement as Assistant Secretary.
    - J[ohn] Van Buren, New York, [New York] to Mr. [Peter Grayson] Washington, n.p., 16 March 1857., 3 pages. ALS. (Box-folder 2:3)
      Regrets Washington's resignation and asks for information he requested earlier.
    - Alex[ander] C. Morton, New York, [New York], to Col. Peter Grayson Washington, Washington, D.C., 6 November 1857., 1 page. ALS. (Box-folder 2:3)
      Needs the particulars of the case before bringing it to the attention of the Secretary; knows Washington rejoices at the Democrats' success in New York.
  - Personal and Business Correspondence, 1858. (Box-folder 2:4)
    - John B. Grayson, Santa Fe, New Mexico to "cousin," Peter Grayson Washington, Washington City, D.C., 29 January 1858., 1 page. ALS. (Box-folder 2:4)
      Sends discharge of William H. Eikern[?], and the necessary papers for a Land Warrant.
    - T[homas] J[ames] D[uncan] Fuller, Second Auditor, Treasury Department, [Washington, D.C.], to Peter Grayson Washington, City of Washington, [D.C.], 27 February 1858., 1 page. LS. (Box-folder 2:4)
      Returns letter of Geo[rge] H. Ambrose.
    - T[homas] J[ames] D[uncan] Fuller, Second Auditor, Treasury Department, [Washington, D.C.], to Messrs. Silas and Edw[ar]d Day, care of Peter Grayson Washington, City of Washington, [D.C.], 30 April 1858., 1 page. LS. (Box-folder 2:4)
      By applying at the office, they can receive payment on their claim against the Rogue River Indians.
    - T[homas] J[ames] D[uncan] Fuller, Second Auditor, Treasury Department, [Washington, D.C.], to Francis Nacerette, care of Peter Grayson Washington, City of Washington, [D.C.], 30 April 1858., 1 page. LS. (Box-folder 2:4)
      By applying at the office, he can receive payment on his claim against the Rogue River Indians.
    - T[homas] J[ames] D[uncan] Fuller, Second Auditor, Treasury Department, [Washington, D.C.], to John Anderson, care of Peter Grayson Washington, City of Washington, [D.C.], 30 April 1858., 1 page. LS. (Box-folder 2:4)
    - A. W. Thompson, Philad[elphia] [Pennsylvania], to Peter Grayson Washington, n.p., 9 May 1858., 1 page. ALS. (Box-folder 2:4)
      Needs certain papers before he sees Senator [James Murray] Mason; feels it advisable for the bill to be part of the General Post Office Bill.
    - Sam[uel] L. Harris, Washington, D.C., to Thomas J. Shadden, Lafayette, Oregon, 17 July 1858., 1 page. ALS. (Box-folder 2:4)
      Succeeded in getting an appropriation for Shadden's service as a "Vaguero" in the Fremont-Folsom expedition of 1846-1847, and will inform him when the money is available.
    - D[avid] S[mith] Terry, Sacramento, [California], to L. Q. Washington, n.p., 29 December 1858., 1 page. ALS. (Box-folder 2:4)
      Introduces Mr. P. A. Athern, who Terry has advised to employ Washington in a case before the Commissioners of the Land Office.
  - Personal and Business Correspondence, 1859. (Box-folder 2:4)
    - Sam[ue]l L. Gouverneur, Jr., Washington City [D.C.], to Peter Grayson Washington, n.p., 27 January 1859., 1 page. ALS. (Box-folder 2:4)
      Sends information on Henry Hodges, who served in 1814 and 1815 for the Bounty Land application of Elizabeth and Henry Hodges.
    - Sam[uel][?] Casey, Washington, [D.C.] to "Dear Sir," n.p., 2 August 1859., 1 page. ALS. (Box-folder 2:4)
      Hopes for a long leave to recover his health; finds a strong sentiment for General [Joseph] Lane in Virginia, North Carolina, and Tennessee; feels the influence of [Stephen A.] Douglas' friends will control the nomination.
    - Salmon] P[ortland] Chase, Cincinnati, [Ohio], to Peter Grayson Washington, Ass[istan]t Sec[retar]y [of the] Treas[ury], [Washington, D.C.], 6 August 1859., 1 page. ALS. (Box-folder 2:4)
      Asks for 3 copies of the California Charts. Including ANS by "A. F. B." 10 August [1859].
    - T[homas] J[ames] D[uncan] Fuller, Second Auditor, Treasury Department, [Washington, D.C.], to G. H. Ambrose, care of Peter Grayson Washington, City of Washington, [D.C.], 9 September 1859., 1 page. LS. (Box-folder 2:4)
      Ambrose will receive the balance due him shortly.
  - Personal and Business Correspondence, 1860., 8 items. (Box-folder 2:4)
    - Jos[eph] C. Potts, The Trenton Locomotive and Manufacturing Co., Trenton, New Jersey, to Peter Grayson Washington, n.p., 27 February 1860., 3 pages. ALS. (Box-folder 2:4)
      Discusses sentiment in New Jersey for [Stephen A.] Douglas and [James] Guthrie, and tactics for the [Democratic] Convention; comments on the North-South political crisis.
    - J. S. Little, Portland, [Maine?], to Peter Grayson Washington, n.p., 18 March 1860., 3 pages. ALS. (Box-folder 2:4)
      Expresses sympathy on death of Mr. [David A.] Bokee, prefers [Stephen A.] Douglas for President over "your candidate," but would be resigned if Mr. [James] Guthrie won.
    - W[illia]m Henry Trescot, Acting Secretary, Department of State, Washington, [D.C.], to Peter Grayson and L. Q. Washington, Washington City, [D.C.], 11 July 1860., 1 page. LS. (Box-folder 2:4)
      Mr. Trevitt's claim for medical aid to American seamen while U.S. consul at Valparaiso, [Chile] has been disallowed.
    - [?] Napoleon Zermon[?], New York, [New York], to Peter Grayson Washington, n.p., 10 August [18]60., 2 pages. LS. (Box-folder 2:4)
      Needs Washington's advice on whether to sell his claim.
    - [?] Napoleon Zermon, Washington, D.C., to G. P. [sic] Washington, n.p., 24 September 1860., 1 page. ALS. (Box-folder 2:4)
      Introduces Mr. Stephen P. Mirzan[?], who wants the position of Dragoman near the Sublime Port.
    - Ja[me]s B. Campbell, Charleston, [?], to Peter Grayson and L. Q. Washington, n.p., 25 November [18]60., 1 page. ALS. (Box-folder 2:4)
      Has not received an acknowledgement of sending them a claim on Mr. Hurst[?].
    - W[illiam] W[allace] Phelps, Reolburg, Minnesota, to Peter Grayson Washington, n.p., 9 December 1860., 1 page. ALS. (Box-folder 2:4)
      Needs to know how the "present disturbed conditions" will affect the conducting of public business; received Washington's circular.
    - Geo[rge] P. Kane, n.p., to [Peter Grayson Washington], n.p., [1860?]., 4 pages. ALS. (Box-folder 2:4)
      Discusses Mr. [James] Guthrie's chances with the Maryland delegation in light of his support of the iron and granite industries.